Guide to the Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, Office of the Dean records, 1911-2006 UA.25.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Federal Research Support, 1982 (Box 57)
  - Federations, 1980-1982 (Box 57)
  - Few Federation, 1975-1982 (Box 57)
  - Financial Aid, 1980-1982 (Box 57)
  - Fixtures, Furniture, Etc., 1980 (Box 57)
  - Fulbright-Hays Scholarship Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 57)
  - Geology, 1980-1983 (Box 57)
  - Germanic Languages and Literature, 1983 (Box 57)
  - Germanic Languages and Literature, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
  - Gift Records, 1979-1983 (Box 58)
  - Graduate Awards Request, 1982-1983 (Box 58)
  - Graduate Faculty Executive Committee, 1975-1983 (Box 58)
  - Graduate School, 1979-1983 (Box 58)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1980-1981 (Box 58)
  - Graduation, 1983 (Box 58)
  - Graduation List, 1983 (Box 58)
  - Graduation, 1982-1983 (Box 58)
  - Graduation Lists, 1979-1983 (Box 58)
  - Grants, Fellowships, Scholarships, 1974-1978 (Box 58)
  - GTE Focus Program, 1982 (Box 58)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 58)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
  - History, 1980-1983 (Box 58)
  - Honors Program, 1981 (Box 58)
  - Housing, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
  - Human Development, 1980-1983 (Box 58)
  - Human Relations Course, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1980-1983 (Box 59)
  - Independent Study, 1976-1980 (Box 59)
  - Interdisciplinary Course and Faculty Seminar, 1979-1981 (Box 59)
  - Interdisciplinary Programs, 1982 (Box 59)
  - International Faculty Lecture Bureau, 1981 (Box 59)
  - International Fertility Program, 1980 (Box 59)
  - International Studies, 1980-1983 (Box 59)
  - International Studies: Directorship, General Information, 1980 (Box 59)
  - Inter-View, 1983 (Box 59)
  - Invitations, 1974-1982 (Box 59)
  - Islamic and Arabic Studies, 1980-1982 (Box 59)
  - Jacksonville Education and Administration Program, 1980 (Box 60)
  - Judicial Board RESTRICTED (Box 60)
  - Judicial Board RESTRICTED (Box 60)
  - Kennedy, Joseph (Box 60)
  - Language Laboratory, 1980-1982 (Box 60)
  - Latin Honors, 1981-1982 (Box 60)
  - Leaves and Sabbaticals: General Information, 1982-1983 (Box 60)
  - Leonardo DaVinci Award, 1981 (Box 60)
  - Lewis, Harold, 1974-1980 (Box 60)
  - Library, 1975-1983 (Box 60)
  - MacAnderson Scholarship Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 60)
  - Macy Foundation, Talk, 1981 (Box 60)
  - Management Sciences, 1980-1982 (Box 60)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1981-1983 (Box 60)
  - Marine Laboratory Notebook, 1981 (Box 60)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1980 (Box 61)
  - Mathematics, 1980-1983 (Box 61)
  - Medical and Allied Health Education, 1976 (Box 61)
  - Medieval and Renaissance Studies, Committee on, 1979-1983 (Box 61)
  - Methodist Board of Higher Education, 1974-1981 (Box 61)
  - Microelectronics Center of North Carolina, MCNC, 1980-1983 (Box 61)
  - Military Science, 1981-1983 (Box 61)
  - Minority Affairs, 1980-1983 (Box 61)
  - Music, 1980-1983 (Box 62)
  - Music: Dr. Boetticher Affair, 1982 (Box 62)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1980-1983 (Box 62)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Summer Stipends, 1981-1983 (Box 62)
  - National Humanities Center, 1977-1983 (Box 62)
  - Naval Science, 1980-1983 (Box 62)
  - New Student Convocation, 1982 (Box 62)
  - New York Arts Program, 1982-1983 (Box 62)
  - Newcombe, Charlotte W. Scholarship, 1981 (Box 62)
  - News Releases: Duke, 1980-1984 (Box 62)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Library, 1981-1982 (Box 62)
  - N. C. Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Nursing Program, 1980-1981 (Box 62)
  - Nursing, School of, 1974-1981 (Box 62)
  - Officers and Staff, 1980 (Box 62)
  - Opportunity Development Center, 1981-1983 (Box 62)
  - Orientation, New Chairmen, Arts and Sciences, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Payroll, 1975-1978 (Box 63)
  - Personnel, 1978-1981 (Box 63)
  - Philosophy, 1980-1983 (Box 63)
  - Physics, 1980-1983 (Box 63)
  - Pi Gamma Mu, 1981 (Box 63)
  - Placement Services, 1980-1981 (Box 63)
  - University Planning Committee, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Policy Manual, 1982-1983 (Box 63)
  - Political Science, 1981-1983 (Box 63)
  - Pre-Law and Pre-Business, 1974-1980 (Box 63)
  - Pre-Major Advising, 1982-1983 (Box 63)
  - Pre-Major Advising Center, 1980-1981 (Box 63)
  - Pre-School, 1981-1982 (Box 63)
  - President, 1979-1983 (Box 64)
  - Primate Center, 1980-1982 (Box 64)
  - Provost, 1980-1983 (Box 64)
  - Provost Group, 1974-1978 (Box 64)
  - Program to Strengthen Medical Science Education, PSMSE: Commonwealth, 1982 (Box 64)
  - PSMSE: Commonwealth, 1981 (Box 64)
  - PSMSE: Commonwealth - Executive Committee, 1980 (Box 64)
  - PSMSE: Commonwealth - Executive Committee, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Psychology, 1980-1983 (Box 65)
  - Public Policy Studies, 1980-1983 (Box 65)
  - Publications Office, 1977-1982 (Box 65)
  - Pye, Chancellor A. K., 1980-1982 (Box 65)
  - Quebec Studies, 1980-1981 (Box 65)
  - Race Relations, Task Force on, 1982 (Box 65)
  - Registrar, 1974-1983 (Box 65)
  - Religion, 1982-1983 (Box 65)
  - Religion, 1980-1981 (Box 66)
  - Religious Activities, 1976 (Box 66)
  - Renovation Procedure and New Construction, 1981-1982 (Box 66)
  - Reorganization, 1982 (Box 66)
  - Research Support Office, 1980-1983 (Box 66)
  - Research Triangle International Visitors Center, 1982 (Box 66)
  - Residential Life, Task Force on, 1980 (Box 66)
  - Residential Policy, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1980 (Box 66)
  - Riviere, Professor Jean, 1981-1982 (Box 66)
  - Rochester, University of, Advisory Meeting of Trustees Council, 1980 (Box 66)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 66)
  - Romance Languages, 1980-1983 (Box 66)
  - ROTC, 1970-1982 (Box 66)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships: General, 1976-1983 (Box 66)
  - Scholarships, Names and Loan Funds, 1963-1977 (Box 66)
  - Science, Technology, and Human Values, 1981-1983 (Box 66)
  - SECID, 1980-1981 (Box 66)
  - Severe Weather Policy, 1982 (Box 66)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1983 (Box 66)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1979-1981 (Box 66)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Slavic Languages, 1980-1983 (Box 67)
  - Smithsonian Institution Radiation Lab Project, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
  - Sociobiology Faculty Study Group, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Sociology, 1980-1983 (Box 67)
  - Society for Applied Anthropology, 1980 (Box 67)
  - South Asian Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 67)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1977-1982 (Box 67)
  - Space Assignment: Trinity College, 1979-1982 (Box 67)
  - Statistics, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
  - Step Symposium, 1982-1983 (Box 67)
  - Student Affairs, 1980-1983 (Box 67)
  - Student Affairs, Task Force on, Student Life, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Study Abroad, 1980-1983 (Box 67)
  - Study of Christian Origins, 1981 (Box 67)
  - Study Skills Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
  - Study Skills and Tutoring, 1978-1980 (Box 67)
  - Summer Session, 1980-1983 (Box 67)
  - Summer Study Abroad, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
  - Summer Transitional Program, 1980-1983 (Box 68)
  - Swahili, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Talent Identification Program, 1981-1983 (Box 68)
  - Teacher-Course Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Teacher Development (Box 68)
  - Teaching Assistants: Graduate, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Teaching Council: Undergraduate, 1982 (Box 68)
  - Teaching Excellence, 1974-1976 (Box 68)
  - Three-College Observatory, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Transportation Management Board, 1980-1983 (Box 68)
  - Triangle Area Research Directors Club, 1981-1982 (Box 68)
  - Trinity College Inventory of Equipment, 1983 (Box 68)
  - Trinity Council, 1980-1981 (Box 68)
  - Tropical Studies, 1980-1981 (Box 68)
  - Trustee List, 1980-1983 (Box 68)
  - Trustees, 1983 RESTRICTED (Box 68)
  - Trustees, 1982 RESTRICTED (Box 68)
  - Trustees, 1981 RESTRICTED (Box 68)
  - Trustees, 1979-1980 RESTRICTED (Box 68)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate Hourly Rates, 1982 (Box 68)
  - Undergraduate Research Assistantship Program, 1976-1980 (Box 68)
  - Undergraduate Teaching Council, 1979-1982 (Box 69)
  - University Architect, 1982 (Box 69)
  - University Technical Support Committee, 1982 (Box 69)
  - Vienna Program, 1979-1981 (Box 69)
  - Warwick Exchange Program, 1974-1981 (Box 69)
  - Washington Semester Program, 1982 (Box 69)
  - WEAL, Women's Equity Action League, 1979-1980 (Box 69)
  - White House Fellowships, 1980-1983 (Box 69)
  - Winston Churchill Scholarship, 1982 (Box 69)
  - Work Study, 1975-1981 (Box 69)
  - Women Administrators in North Carolina Higher Education, 1979-1982 (Box 69)
  - Women in Science and Engineering, Visiting Professorships for, 1982 (Box 69)
  - Women in Science Career Workshop, 1982-1983 (Box 69)
  - Women's Equity Action League, undated (Box 69)
  - Women's Network, 1979-1983 (Box 69)
  - Women's Studies, 1980-1983 (Box 69)
  - Women's Studies Program, Committee on, 1981 (Box 69)
  - Writing and Composition Program, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Year Round Operation Preliminary Report, 1981 (Box 69)
  - Year Round Operations: Responses - Chairmen, 1979-1980 (Box 69)
  - Year Round Operations, TCAS, 1980 (Box 69)
  - Young Writer's Conference, 1983 (Box 69)
  - Zoology, 1980-1983 (Box 69)
  - UFCAS: Executive Committee, 1979-1983 (Box 70)
  - UFCAS: Executive Committee Minutes, 1974-1983 (Box 70)
  - UFCAS: Attendance, 1983-1984 (Box 70)
  - UFCAS: Ballots, 1982-1983 (Box 70)
  - UFCAS: Representatives, 1980-1984 (Box 70)
  - UFCAS: Standing Committees, 1979-1984 (Box 70)
  - UFCAS: Academic Standards Committee, 1979-1983 (Box 70)
  - UFCAS: Admissions and Financial Aid, Committee on, 1983 (Box 70)
  - UFCAS: Admissions and Financial Aid, Committee on, 1980-1982 (Box 71)
  - UFCAS: Advising Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 71)
  - UFCAS: Course Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 71)
  - UFCAS: Curriculum Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 71)
  - UFCAS: Curriculum Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Honors Committee, 1973-1983 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Program II, 1971-1981 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Residential Life Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Study Abroad Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Ad Hoc Committee of the Academic Calendar, 1982-1983 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Ad Hoc Committee on Admissions/Decisions, 1979-1983 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Ad Hoc Committee on Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1983-1984 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Ad Hoc Committee on Health Science Education, 1977-1983 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Ad Hoc Committee Honors Committee, 1980 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Ad Hoc Committee on Honors and Academic Excellence, 1977-1979 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Ad Hoc Committee on Quality of Teaching, 1981-1983 (Box 72)
  - UFCAS: Ad Hoc Review Committee - for Review Structure of UFCAS, 1981-1983 (Box 72)
  - Select Committee on Teaching Evaluation, 1978-1982 (Box 72)
  - Undergraduate Teaching Council, UTC, 1974-1978 (Box 72)
  - UTC Correspondence and Agenda, 1978-1979 (Box 72)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 72)
  - UTC Summary, 1973-1981 (Box 72)
  - UTC, 1973-1974 (Box 72)
  - Proposals, 1973-1974 (Box 72)
  - Extensions Requested for Budget Changes, 1973-1974 (Box 72)
  - Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 72)
  - UTC Membership, 1974-1975 (Box 72)
  - UTC Final Report, 1973-1974 (Box 72)
  - UTC Financial Statements, 1974-1975 (Box 72)
  - UTC Mailing List: Announcements, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - UTC Rating Sheets, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - UTC Award Letters and Proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - Award Letters with Code Number, 1973-1974 (Box 73)
  - UTC Proposals not Supported, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - UTC Letter on Method of Review, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - UTC Announcement, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Extensions/Budget Changes, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - UTC Final Report, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - UTC Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - UTC Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - UTC Award Letters on Proposals, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Proposals not Supported, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Financial Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Extension/Budget Changes, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Proposals Supported, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Final Report, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - UTC Proposals rejected and Correspondence on, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC AV Center, Perkins Library, Correspondence on, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Financial Statements and Grant Extensions, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Correspondence to Council Members, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Extensions/Budget Changes, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Rating Sheets, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Financial Statements, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Announcement, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Proposals not Supported, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Final Reports from Grantees, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Award Letters, Proposals, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Proposals Supported, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - UTC Announcements of Awards and Letters of Acceptance, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC Copies of Proposals Submitted for Support, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC Proposal Rejected and Correspondence on, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC Financial Statements and Grant Extensions, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC Invitations to Apply, 1978-1979 (Box 73)
  - UTC Correspondence to Council Members, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC Final Reports from Grantees, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC Final Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC Announcements of Awards and Letters of Acceptance, 1978-1979 (Box 73)
  - UTC Copies of Proposals Submitted for Support, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC AV Center, Perkins Library Correspondence on, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - UTC Invitation to Faculty to Submit Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 73)
  - UTC Applications, 1980 (Box 73)
  - Academic Support Program, 1979-1981 (Box 73)
  - Army ROTC Establishment, 1980 (Box 73)
  - Army ROTC, 1981-1982 (Box 73)
  - ASDU, 1976-1983 (Box 73)
  - Assistant Deans, 1980-1981 (Box 74)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1976-1983 (Box 74)
  - Athletic Department, 1975-1983 (Box 74)
  - Benenson, Edward, 1976 RESTRICTED *FERPA* (Box 74)
  - Benenson, Edward and Benenson Prize, 1981 (Box 74)
  - Biology Major, 1979 (Box 74)
  - Black/White Relations Student Task Force, 1982 (Box 74)
  - Virginia Bryan, 1978-1982 (Box 74)
  - Bulletin, 1977-1983 (Box 74)
  - Bursar, 1978-1983 (Box 74)
  - Career Counseling, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1977-1978 (Box 74)
  - College Board, 1982 (Box 74)
  - COLOE, 1982 (Box 74)
  - College Venture Program, 1980 (Box 74)
  - Commonwealth Proposal, 1976-1979 (Box 74)
  - Computerized Course Catalog, 1980 (Box 74)
  - Continuing Education, 1977-1983 (Box 74)
  - Continuation Requirements, 1975-1977 (Box 74)
  - Student Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - Counseling Services, Committee on, Ad Hoc, 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1980 (Box 75)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 75)
  - Department Reports, 1980 (Box 75)
  - DUS Handbook, Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1982 (Box 75)
  - DUS, 1975-1981 (Box 75)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminars, 1976-1981 (Box 75)
  - Distinguished Undergraduate Scholars, 1981 (Box 75)
  - Drop/Add Cases, 1980 (Box 75)
  - Receipt Procedure Drop/Add, 1980 (Box 75)
  - A. B. Duke Scholarship, 1976-1981 (Box 75)
  - Duke-UNC International Studies Co-op, 1980-1983 (Box 75)
  - Duke UNC Symposium, undated (Box 75)
  - Durham Technical Institute, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Environmental Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 75)
  - Extended Staff, 1975-1977 (Box 75)
  - Federation Proposal: Strobel, 1980-1981 (Box 75)
  - Federations, 1977-1983 (Box 75)
  - Federation Task Force, Dean's Advisory, 1976-1982 (Box 75)
  - John M. Fein, 1975-1979 (Box 75)
  - Foreign Language Institute, 1983 (Box 75)
  - Freshmen Advisers, 1978-1983 (Box 75)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1977-1983 (Box 75)
  - Friedl, 1979-1983 (Box 75)
  - Government Excess Program, 1981 (Box 76)
  - Handicapped Persons, Regulations Regarding, 1977 (Box 76)
  - Health Professions Advising, 1976-1983 (Box 76)
  - Hanks, Shirley, 1978-1981 (Box 76)
  - Independent Study, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 76)
  - Insurance-Student, 1977-1982 (Box 76)
  - IR Designation, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - Interns, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - IUCR, 1975-1976 (Box 76)
  - Joint Degree BA/MA, 1982 (Box 76)
  - Judicial Board Appeals, 1979-1980 RESTRICTED (Box 76)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1974-1980 (Box 76)
  - Management Science, 1977-1982 (Box 76)
  - Media Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - Medical Science Education, Program to Strengthen, 1977-1979 (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Memo and Letters, 1975-1982 (Box 76)
  - Mid-Semester Grades, 1977-1979 (Box 76)
  - Minority Affairs, Office of, 1975-1983 (Box 76)
  - Elizabeth Nathans, 1976-1982 (Box 76)
  - Navy ROTC, 1980-1982 (Box 76)
  - NC High School of Math and Science, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Officers Education Committee, 1977-1981 (Box 77)
  - Pilot Advising Program, 1979 (Box 77)
  - Pre-Law/Pre-Divinity Proposal, 1981 (Box 77)
  - Reauthorization Bill, 1980 (Box 77)
  - Registrar, 1976-1981 (Box 77)
  - Registrar Review, 1982 (Box 77)
  - Registration, 1980 (Box 77)
  - Ripley, Dana, 1978-1979 (Box 77)
  - Scholarship Virginia/Carolinas Society, 1977 (Box 77)
  - Scholarships, 1975-1982 (Box 77)
  - Southern University Conference, 1978 (Box 77)
  - Staff Meetings, TCAS, 1975-1982 (Box 77)
  - Strobel, Howard, 1975-1983 (Box 77)
  - Student Affairs Advisory Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 77)
  - Student Affairs-Trinity College Task Force, 1982 (Box 77)
  - Student Affairs-Peggy Sackett Report, 1976 (Box 77)
  - Student Life-Moore, 1977 (Box 77)
  - Office of Student Affairs, 1975-1982 (Box 77)
  - Study Rooms, 1980-1982 (Box 77)
  - Summer Programs for Freshmen, 1982 (Box 77)
  - STP: Summer Transitional Program, 1975-1983 (Box 77)
  - System Design Study, 1978 (Box 78)
  - Title IX, 1976 (Box 78)
  - Title IX Mailing, 1976 (Box 78)
  - WP/WF Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 78)
  - TCAS Council, 1980 (Box 78)
  - Task Force Year Round Operation, 1980 (Box 78)
  - Teacher Course Evaluation, 1977-1982 (Box 78)
  - Transfer Evaluation Procedure, 1978 (Box 78)
  - Truman Scholarship, 1977 (Box 78)
  - Tutorial Program, 1976-1981 (Box 78)
  - Undergraduate Admissions and Financial Aid Committee, 1982 (Box 78)
  - Financial Aid Budget Study, 1977-1978 (Box 78)
  - Undergraduate Teaching Council, 1981-1982 (Box 78)
  - University Council, 1976 (Box 78)
  - University Courses, 1975-1976 (Box 78)
  - University Marshal, 1976-1982 (Box 78)
  - University Schedule Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 78)
  - Visiting Student Program, 1978-1982 (Box 78)
  - X-Rated Film Policy, 1977 (Box 78)
  - Veterans Office, 1978 (Box 78)
  - Woodlands Institute, undated (Box 78)
  - Title IX: Committee of the Athletic Council General Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 78)
  - Title IX: Meetings and Documents, 1976 (Box 78)
  - Student Records [policy], 1970 (Box 78)
  - W Grades, 1976-1980 (Box 78)
  - OSRs, 1966-1971 RESTRICTED (Box 78)
  - Faculty, 1962-1976 (Box 78)
  - Title IX, 1978-1981, Athletics, 1983 (Box 78)
  - Transition from the Woman's College and Trinity College to Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, 1968-1975 (Box 78)
  - A-21, 1979-1981 (Box 79)
  - AAC Project on the Status and Education of Women, 1979-1980 (Box 79)
  - Academic Administration, 1981 (Box 79)
  - Academic Affairs Committee: Board of Trustees, 1984-1985 (Box 79)
  - Academic Betterments Fund, 1982 (Box 79)
  - Academic Computing Systems, 1981-1984 (Box 79)
  - Academic Council: Minutes and Agenda, 1984 (Box 79)
  - Ace National Commission on Higher Education, 1981 (Box 79)
  - Admissions, 1984-1985 (Box 79)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid, University Committee on Undergraduate, 1981-1984 (Box 79)
  - Aging and Human Development, University Council on, 1982-1984 (Box 79)
  - Alcohol Abuse, 1980-1985 (Box 79)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 79)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1984 (Box 80)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1980-1983 (Box 80)
  - Anatomy Department, 1975-1981 (Box 80)
  - Anthropology Department, 1984 (Box 80)
  - Anthropology Planning Documents, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Art Department, 1983-1984 (Box 80)
  - Art Planning, 1984 (Box 80)
  - Art Museum, 1984 (Box 80)
  - A and S Campaign, 1984 (Box 80)
  - ASDU Legislation Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 80)
  - Associated Students of Duke University, ASDU, 1984 (Box 80)
  - Association of American Publishers, Inc., 1983 (Box 80)
  - Association of Departments of English, ADE Conference, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Athletics, 1982-1984 (Box 80)
  - Australian Fellowships, 1980 (Box 80)
  - Authors-Arts and Sciences-Cocktails and Dinner, 1981 (Box 80)
  - Baldwin Federation, 1981-1983 (Box 80)
  - Basic Research in the Behavioral and Social Sciences, Committee on, 1980 (Box 80)
  - Benenson Awards, 1983-1985 (Box 80)
  - Black/White Relations, Task Force on, 1982 (Box 80)
  - Blaydon, Dr. Colin, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Botany Department, 1983-1984 (Box 80)
  - Botany Planning, 1982-1984 (Box 80)
  - Boycott, 1980 (Box 80)
  - Brookings Institution Fellowships, 1982 (Box 80)
  - Budget, 1983-1985 (Box 80)
  - Business, Finance and Law, Vice President for, 1985 (Box 80)
  - Career Choices Conference, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Cellular and Molecular Biology, 1979-1980 (Box 80)
  - Chairman's Council, 1984 (Box 80)
  - Chancellor, 1982-1983 (Box 81)
  - Chemistry Department, 1983-1984 (Box 81)
  - Chemistry Planning, 1981-1984 (Box 81)
  - China Exchange Program, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Class Honors Letters, 1983-1985 (Box 81)
  - Classical Studies Planning Documents, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Clotfelter, Charles-Vice Provost for Academic Policy and Planning, 1983-1985 (Box 81)
  - College Board, 1982 (Box 81)
  - College Venture Program, 1980 (Box 81)
  - COLOE Administrative Committee, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Commencement, 1984-1986 (Box 81)
  - Commonwealth, 1980-1983 (Box 81)
  - Commonwealth Fund Appointment, 1980-1983 (Box 81)
  - Communications Network, 1981 (Box 81)
  - Comparative Area Studies, 1975-1983 (Box 81)
  - Comparative Studies of Immigration and Ethnicity, 1980-1981 (Box 81)
  - Computer Aided Instruction, 1979-1983 (Box 81)
  - Computer Science, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Computer Science Planning, 1982 (Box 81)
  - Computer Sciences Enterprise Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 81)
  - Computer Systems Information, 1982 (Box 81)
  - Computerized Management Information System, 1983 (Box 81)
  - Conference on Hatred, 1985 (Box 81)
  - Continuing Education, 1983-1985 (Box 81)
  - Counsel, University, 1977-1985 (Box 81)
  - Courses by Football Players, 1982 (Box 81)
  - Crossland, Dr. Fred, 1981-1985 (Box 81)
  - Dance Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 81)
  - Dean of Arts and Sciences and Trinity College, 1979-1980 (Box 81)
  - Deans Conference, 1985 (Box 81)
  - Deans Conference, 1979-1985 (Box 82)
  - Deans Council, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
  - Deans Search [generic], 1984-1985 (Box 82)
  - Decentralization of Personnel, 1983 (Box 82)
  - Departmental Incentive Plan, 1983 (Box 82)
  - Development, 1984-1985 (Box 82)
  - Distinguished Alumnus Award, 1981 (Box 82)
  - Distinguished Arts and Sciences Instructor Program, 1980 (Box 82)
  - Divinity School, 1976-1984 (Box 82)
  - Drama Program Planning, 1984 (Box 82)
  - Dreyfus, Camille and Henry, Distinguished Scholar Lectures, 1981-1982 (Box 82)
  - Duke Humanities Review, 1980-1983 (Box 82)
  - Duke Investment Club, 1983 (Box 82)
  - Early Identification Program, EIP, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
  - Economics Department, 1984 (Box 82)
  - Economics Planning, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
  - Education Accreditation, 1985 (Box 82)
  - Education Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
  - Education, Program in, 1984 (Box 82)
  - Emeriti Space, 1984-1986 (Box 82)
  - Engineering, 1984 (Box 82)
  - English Department, 1983-1984 (Box 83)
  - English Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 83)